DOUG RUSH

Full-Stack Web Developer

Find me on Github https://github.com/rushdm15

rushdm15@gmail.com

2920 English Avenue, Louisville, KY, 20206

IN A NUTSHELL

Full-Stack Web Dev, Army Veteran, Entrepreneur, Farmer What do I bring to the table?

I have 5+ years of diverse leadership and management experience from the US Army and my personal Amazon start-up, as well as managing the family farm. Because I enjoy meaningful and productive work, I trained 600 hours in full-stack web development, learning:

Front-End Web Development (HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, & more)

Back-End Web Development (API, MongoDB, AWS, NodeJS, React, React Native, Angular, & more)

I don't want...

...just another job. I want to solve problems and make people's lives better in a community that shares my passion for technology.

EXPERIENCE

Livestock Farmer — 2016 - Present

Managed the family farm and was in charge of three workers

Entrepreneur, Krikiti Protein LLC — 2016—2018

Started Amazon business that sold innovative protein bars manufactured under my own brand name

Infantryman, Virginia National Guard — 2011—2016

Served five years in the Army National Guard while I simultaneously completed college

EDUCATION

Virginia Military Institute — BS Economics & Business, Class of 2015

CareerFoundry — Online Coding Bootcamp, September 2020—February 2021